--- Model Parameters & Output Control Experiments ---

[Task 1] Testing Temperature:

Running with temperature=0.0...
Output (temp=0.0): [SIMULATED - temp=0.0] Regular performance reviews are essential for aligning employee goals with company objectives, providing constructive feedback, and identifying areas for professional development. They ensure consistent communication and help maintain productivity.

Running with temperature=1.0...
Output (temp=1.0): [SIMULATED - temp=1.0] Imagine a ship without a compassùthat's a company without performance reviews! They totally transform the workplace by sparking amazing conversations, boosting morale sky-high, and unleashing the hidden potential of every single team member in unexpected ways!

[Task 2] Testing max_tokens:

Running with max_tokens=15...
Output (max_tokens=15): [SIMULATED] Regular performance reviews are essential for aligning employee goals with company

[Task 3] Testing stop sequence:

Running with stop=[','] (should stop at the first comma)...
Output (stop=[',']): [SIMULATED] Regular performance reviews are essential for aligning employee goals with company objectives

Experiments completed. Results saved to outputs/parameter_experiments.json
